CDoom is a Doom for Communicator, Chrystal platform.

Original Doom by ID Software, 1997.
SDL port by Sam Lantinga, 1998.
Symbian OS port by Hannu Viitala & Markus Mertama, 2001. Version 1.00.

INSTALLING
- Install sis package. Installation puts files in "\CDoom" and "\system\apps\launcher" folders.
- You have to copy some wad file in "\CDoom" folder. Shareware IWad file can be found from: http://www.idsoftware.com/archives/doomarc.html
- Doom is started from Extras
- You will need ~3.3 Mb to play CDoom, if you do not have that much memory currently available, please close all you open documents and reboot device by removing a battery for a while. Some levels may need even more memory to act properly. Due the limited resources you do not have audio, either netgame, yet.

PLAYING
- Full screen is enabled from: "options/screen size".
- Function keys are used as follows: F1=chr+q, F2=chr+w,..., F8=chr+i, F9=chr+a,..., F12=chr+d

CDoom uses GPL licence. See text files in "CDoom" folder for more info.
You can get the sources for CDoom, SDL for Epoc and Launcher from: www.mbnet.fi/~haviital

There is no warranty for the program. Do not use this program or play CDoom if you have, or will have, problems to do so.

Happy killing!

