4.9.2001 HV 

CDOOM
=====

This Doom port is based strongly on SDLDoom. Some Nokia9210 specific changes 
and extra source files were added to the SDLDoom source tree. It is not any 
more compatible with SDLDoom, so the project was renamed to CDoom.

Like SdlDoom, CDoom uses SDL library which I have ported to Epoc.

CDoom uses GPL license. See "copying.epoc.txt".

Not implemented: 
- network game 
- sounds 

Known bugs: 
- Bunny screen do not work 

Building: 
- build SDL first 
- cd to \CDoom\epoc 
- abld build armi urel 
- build launcher

Other: 
- Sorry, there are not much comments in the code. This was made as a hobby and nowadays 
  there are very little time for these things:-( Recommended to use some file compare tool
  for tracking changes.
- Most of the porting problems was caused by struct aligment problems and implicit 
  definition of "char" in different compilers. Solution was to use "attribute packed" 
  for some structs and explicit "signed char" type.
- For printing debug output to serial port, define EPOC_DEBUG_PRINT macro. It e.g. 
  redefines printf(). 
- There are only one assembler optimised function: FixedMul() 
  
Authors:

Hannu Viitala 
email:hannu.j.viitala@mbnet.fi 
homepage:www.mbnet.fi/~haviital (for sources of CDoom, Launcher and SDL for Epoc)

Markus Mertama
email: w@iki.fi
